A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (L-Z), Accession 2021:051 FA1790
Rockefeller Archive Center
John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (L-Z), Accession 2021:051
2001-2017
Rockefeller Archive Center
John S. and James L. Knight Foundation
FA1790
31.14 Cubic Feet (82 containers)
2.8 Gigabytes
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains grant records (L-Z) for Knight communities (Miami, Philadelphia, Detroit, San Jose, Charlotte, Akron, Macon, St. Paul, Columbus, Grand Forks, and Milledgeville) with a focus on Knight grant program areas including Community and National initiatives, Journalism and Media Innovation, Art, Technology, Learning and Impact, and Trustee-Advised grants. Most grant records include information about the purpose of the grant, the amount gifted, and a final report (where applicable). Each grant has its own grant number which usually represents the year the grant application was filed followed by a unique identifier.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in series according to various Knight program areas:
Series 1: Community and National Initiatives
Series 2: Journalism and Media Innovation
Series 3: Arts
Series 4: Technology and Media Innovation
Series 5: Learning and Impact
Series 6: Other
Series 6.1: Trustee-Advised Grant Program
Series 6.2: Emergency/Impact Fund
Series 6.3: Communication
Series 6.4: Membership
San Jose (Calif.); Miami (Fla.); Social media; Artificial intelligence; Akron (Ohio); Journalism; Charlotte (N.C.); Macon (Ga.); Tallahassee (Fla.); Art; Campaigns, Election -- News media coverage; Voting
- Community and National Initiatives, 2001-2017; 1
  Scope and Contents
  The Community and National Initiatives program focuses on enhancing local communities by attracting talent, encouraging economic opportunities, and promoting community engagement. This series also contains grants that fall under the Knight Cities Challenge in which grants awarded under this challenge benefit one of the 26 Knight communities and focus on talent, opportunity, or engagement.
  - Lancaster County Community Foundation - 2017 Knight Community Information Lab Winner (2017-54657) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Open in 2027
  - Latin American Venture Capital Association - Miami Conference (2014-49449) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Restricted - Open in 2024
  - LaunchCode Foundation - LaunchCode Miami (2014-49832), 2014-2016 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Restricted - Open in 2026
  - Leadership Akron - Destination Akron (2017-54436) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Leadership Akron - Civic Solutions Laboratory (2015-50305) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Restricted - Open in 2025
  - Leadership Inc, dba Leadership Philadelphia - Connectors and Keepers (2015-50550), 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Legacy Foundation Inc. - On the Table Gary (2017-53757) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Legacy Foundation Inc. - Vacant Property Data, Gary (2013-46578), 2011-2013 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Restricted - Open in 2023
  - Legacy Foundation Inc. - Supplemental Grant to Donor Advised Fund (2009-0262), 2009-2016 (Box 2, Folder 14-17)
  - Lenders for Community Development - Individual Development Accounts (2003-0193), 2002-2008 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Assist 150 low-income families in saving for their own or their children's college education.
  - Lexington Downtown Development Authority - Parking Lot Diaries: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52503) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Lexington Public Library Foundation - Pheonix Forward: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52502), 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Liberty Hill Foundation - Los Angeles City Budget Resource (2013-46398), 2011-2013 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Little Giant Creative - A Dream Deferred - Philadelphia Redlining: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54206), 2014-2017 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Little Giant Creative - The Institute of Hip Hop Entrepreneurship: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52513), 2013-2017 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporation - Civic Commons Community Partners Capacity Building (2016-53466) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Local Label - Screenprint Showdown (2015-51658) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Local Projects, LLC - MyCity Pre-Development Market Research (2015-51290) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Long Beach Community Foundation - On the Table Long Beach, California (2017-53762) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - LR 13-81 LLC dba MiLine - The Ludlum Trail Master Plan (2015-51892), 2016 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Macon Arts Alliance - Mill Hill Cultural District Planning and Community Land Trust (2016-52363) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Macon Arts Alliance - Artist Residency Program, Mill Hill Arts Village (2015-51311) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Macon-Bibb County Urban Development Authority - Macon Action Plan Economic Snapshot Update (2017-55174) (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Macon-Bibb County Urban Development Authority - Macon-Bibb County Transit Study (2017-55262) (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Made by Little LLC - Uncovering America's Civic Commons (2015-51873), 2013-2015 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Manatee Community Foundation - Supplemental Grant to Donor Advised Fund (2009-0255), 2009-2016 (Box 5, Folder 68-69)
  - Manatee County Government - Speak Up Bradenton: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54365) (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Mangrove Labs LLC - Miami Civic User Testing Group: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52509), 2014-2016 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Manhattan Institute for Policy Research - Future of Cities Symposia (2017-54720), 2015-2017 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Mayor's Training Center, Urban League of Lexington-Fayette County - One Community, One Voice (2003-0326), 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    Reading proficiency program.
  - McColl Center for Visual Art - Collaborative Leadership Training Pilot Program, Charlotte (2017-53852) (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - M and D Consulting, LLC - NewCo Miami (2016-53068) (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - MDC Inc. - State of the South (2017-54042) (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Mercer University - Innovation Corridor (2012-0228), 2010-2017 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Mesh, LLC - Making Together: A Makerspace Co-Design Toolkit (2015-51735), 2013-2015 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Methodist Home of the South Georgia Conference - Emergency Care Facility for Foster Children (2004-0209), 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - M.I.A. Group - MIA Music Summit: Where Music and Technology Meet (2014-47986), 2012-2014 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - MIA Collective - Sime MIA (2016-53001), 2013-2016 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - MIA Collective - MIA Music Summit (2015-50389), 2012-2015 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - MIA Collective - Sime MIA Summits (2015-51558), 2013-2015 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - MIA Collective - Wayra Demo Day (2014-49835), 2012-2014 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - MIA Collective - Sime MIA (2013-45570), 2011-2015 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - MIAMade Inc. - 4th Annual Maker Faire Miami (2017-53775) (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - MIAMade Inc. - Maker City Miami (2017-54425) (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Miami Made LLC - The Founder Powered Collective for a Thriving Miami Startup Ecosystem (2016-53607), 2016-2017 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - MIAMade Inc. - The MANO Initiative (2015-51482), 2015-2016 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - MIAMade Inc. - Miami Makers Initiative (2014-48700), 2012-2014 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Miami Center for Architecture and Design, Inc. - Livestreaming Project (2014-50023) (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Miami Dade College Foundation Inc. - Idea Center (2013-46350), 2012-2016 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Miami-Dade County - CityMart (2015-51136) (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Miami-Dade Entrepreneurial Development Organization - Venture Hive's Accelerator Startup (2014-49816) (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Miami Design Preservation League Inc. - Barbara Capitman Memorial (2013-43239), 2011-2013 (Box 12, Folder 151)
  - Miami-Dade Public Library System - Interactive Learning Space for Digital Media (2011-0117), 2011-2013 (Box 12, Folder 152)
  - Miami Downtown Development Authority - Biscayne Green: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52508), 2014-2017 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Miami Finance Forum - Entrepreneurship and Finance Program Series (2015-51578), 2013-2015 (Box 12, Folder 155)
  - Miami Foundation - On the Table Miami (2017-53760) (Box 12, Folder 161)
  - Miami Foundation - The Urban Consulate (2017-53839) (Box 12, Folder 163)
  - Miami Foundation - Augmented Reality and Cities Fund Initial Contribution (2017-54325) (Box 13, Folder 167)
  - Miami Foundation - W. Gerald Austen Endowed Chair in Polymer Science and Polymer Engineering at the University of Akron (2016-53086), 2016-2017 (Box 14, Folder 183)
  - Miami Foundation - My Miami Story (2016-53270) (Box 14, Folder 188)
  - Miami Foundation - Museum Park (2015-50317), 2013-2015 (Box 15, Folder 198)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Charlotte Canopy Restoration Fund (2015-51878), 2013-2017 (Box 16, Folder 206)
  - Miami Foundation - Knight Reimagining the Civic Commons Fund (2015-51929), 2015-2017 (Box 16, Folder 208)
  - Miami Foundation - Museum Park (2014-49203), 2012-2014 (Box 17, Folder 220)
  - Miami Foundation - Walk Your City, San Jose and Lexington (2014-50116), 2012-2015 (Box 17, Folder 225)
  - Miami Foundation - eMerge Americas (2013-43004), 2011-2013 (Box 18, Folder 228)
  - Miami Foundation - RokkMiami 2013 (2013-45352), 2011-2013 (Box 18, Folder 229)
  - Miami Foundation - Our Miami Initiative, National Urban Fellow (2013-46996), 2012-2014 (Box 19, Folder 237)
  - Miami Foundation - Giving Day Initiative, Miami (2013-46656), 2011-2015 (Box 19, Folder 239)
  - Miami Foundation - WhereBy.Us Civic Incubator Prototype (2013-47734), 2012-2014 (Box 20, Folder 246)
  - Miami Foundation - Museum Park (2013-47753), 2012-2014 (Box 20, Folder 247)
  - Miami Foundation - Kiva Detroit (2011-0144), 2010-2015 (Box 21, Folder 257)
  - Miami Herald Charities, Inc. - 2018 Silver Knight Awards (2017-54702) (Box 21, Folder 259)
  - Miami Herald Charities, Inc. - El Nuevo Herald Silver Knight Awards (2015-51525), 2014-2017 (Box 22, Folder 260)
  - Miami Herald Charities, Inc. - Silver Knight Awards (2013-44409), 2011-2014 (Box 22, Folder 261)
  - Miami Herald Charities, Inc. - Silver Knight Awards (2013-47462), 2012-2016 (Box 22, Folder 262)
  - Miami Museum of Science - Science Barge at Frost (2017-54075) (Box 22, Folder 268)
  - Miami Soup - Miami Soup (2013-47279), 2012-2014 (Box 23, Folder 272)
  - Michigan Historic Preservation Network - Brick and Beam Detroit, Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50664) (Box 23, Folder 275)
  - Middle Georgia Regional Library - PRIME TIME Literacy Initiative (2017-54712) (Box 23, Folder 280)
  - Midtown Detroit, Inc. - Community and Stakeholder Engagement (2017-55248) (Box 23, Folder 281)
  - Midtown, Inc. - Minimum Grid: Maximum Impact, Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50698), 2013-2016 (Box 23, Folder 282)
  - Migration Policy Institute - Civic Engagement and Positive Human Relations (2011-0111), 2010-2013 (Box 24, Folder 283)
  - Minneapolis-Saint Paul Region Economic Development Partnership - MSP Hello (2016-53436) (Box 24, Folder 287)
    A network-based initiative to connect new residents to local events and programming.
  - Minnesota E-Democracy - Scaling Up Public Neighborhood Forums (2011-0364), 2010-2014 (Box 24, Folder 292)
  - Minnesota Historical Society - Somali and Minnesota: Opening Weekend Public Programs (2017-55178) (Box 24, Folder 293)
  - Mississippi State University Foundation - Witnessing the Beach: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54595) (Box 25, Folder 301)
  - MIT Enterprise Forum, Inc. - South Florida Sponsorship (2013-46953), 2011-2014 (Box 25, Folder 302)
  - Municipal Arts Society of New York - Committee on Urban Entrepreneurship (2015-50475) (Box 26, Folder 317)
  - Municipal Arts Society of New York - The Swings: An Exercise in Musical Cooperation (2015-50603), 2013-2017 (Box 26, Folder 318)
  - The Musicant Group - Front Lawn Placemaking Platform: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52519), 2013-2016 (Box 26, Folder 325)
  - Naomi Fisher Performance Works - Outdoor Art Performances (2008-0232), 2008-2013 (Box 27, Folder 330)
  - National Association of City Transportation Officials - Accelerating the Transformation of Downtown San Jose's Streets and Bikeways (2017-53828) (Box 27, Folder 336)
  - National Association of City Transportation Officials - Leadership NACTO and Designing Cities Conference (2017-54543) (Box 27, Folder 337)
  - National Association of City Transportation Officials - Designing Cities Conference (2016-52409) (Box 27, Folder 338)
  - National Association of City Transportation Officials - A Better Bike Network, San Jose (2017-55193) (Box 27, Folder 339)
  - National Association of Latino Elected Officials - Women Naturalization Pilot (2013-42757), 2011-2013 (Box 28, Folder 343)
  - National Center for Civic Innovation - The GovLab, New York University, Open Data 500 (2013-47073), 2010-2013 (Box 28, Folder 344)
  - National Constitution Center - Headed to the White House Exhibition (2015-51945), 2015-2016 (Box 28, Folder 346)
  - National Council of La Raza - Citizenship Savings and Loan Demonstration Project (2013-45330), 2011-2014 (Box 28, Folder 347)
  - The National Governors Association Center for Best Practices - Building Successful Innovation Hubs to Ensure Economic Growth and Community Vitality (2013-46980), 2012-2013 (Box 29, Folder 357)
  - National Parks Conservation Association - Analysis of Economic Impact of Proposed Ocmulgee National Park and Preserve (2014-50139), 2012-2015 (Box 29, Folder 361)
  - National Partnership for New Americans - 2013 National Immigration Integration Conference (NICC) (2013-46600) (Box 29, Folder 362)
  - Navicent Health Foundation Inc. - Macon Children's Hospital (2017-54384), 2014-2017 (Box 29, Folder 367)
  - Neighbor.ly Corporation - Crowdfunding Platform (2012-3559), 2011-2014 (Box 30, Folder 368)
  - Network for Teaching Entrepreneurship - Startup Tech (2017-53745) (Box 30, Folder 370)
  - Network for Teaching Entrepreneurship - Digital Classroom Initiative (2013-46488), 2012-2014 (Box 30, Folder 371)
  - New Leaders Council - New Leaders Council, Miami (2013-45267), 2011-2013 (Box 30, Folder 375)
  - New Leaders Council - New Leaders Council, Philadelphia (2013-47726), 2012-2016 (Box 30, Folder 376)
  - NewME Inc. - Minority Entrepreneurship Accelerator (2017-53751) (Box 30, Folder 377)
  - New Mexico Community Foundation - Increase News Content (2013-26358), 2011-2013 (Box 30, Folder 379)
  - The New School - Support for Digital Equity Work in Detroit (2017-54623) (Box 30, Folder 383)
  - New Orleans Startup Fund Inc. - PowerMoves, Miami (2015-51339), 2013-2015 (Box 31, Folder 392)
  - New Town Macon Inc. - Pop-Up Garage Park: A 2017 Knight Cities Winner (2017-54178) (Box 32, Folder 395)
  - New Town Macon Inc. - Ocmulgee Heritage Trail (2017-54870) (Box 32, Folder 396)
  - New Town Macon Inc. - Pop-Up Minimum Grid: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-54506), 2014-2016 (Box 32, Folder 397)
  - New York Restoration Project - Resilience in the Public Realm: Planning and Development (2013-47658), 2013-2014 (Box 32, Folder 411)
  - New York University, Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service - Multi-School, Multi-Disciplinary Technology Network (2012-2265), 2010-2015 (Box 33, Folder 415)
  - New City Inc. - Public Space and Public Life Series (2014-49751) (Box 33, Folder 419)
  - Next City - The Shared City Column (2013-46499), 2011-2016 (Box 33, Folder 420)
  - NiteCap Media, LLC - NiteCap Live (2017-54602) (Box 33, Folder 423)
  - Non-Profit Housing Association of Northern California (NPH) - Building Community Engagement in San Jose (2017-54340) (Box 34, Folder 425)
  - Nonprofit Technology Enterprise Network - Charlotte Digital Fellows (2015-50978) (Box 34, Folder 426)
  - North Akron Community Development Corporation - North Hill Development (2017-54611) (Box 34, Folder 427)
  - Northeast Entrepreneur Fund Inc. - Local Entrepreneur Skills (2007-0153), 2007-2016 (Box 34, Folder 432-434)
  - North Limestone Community Development Corporation - Plant and Play: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54229) (Box 35, Folder 438)
  - North Limestone Community Development Corporation - Northside Common Market (2015-50596), 2015-2016 (Box 35, Folder 439)
  - Ohio and Erie Canalway Coalition - iTowpath, Towpath Trail (2015-51780) (Box 36, Folder 446)
  - Ohio and Erie Canalway Coalition - Lock 4 and Route 59 Pedestrian Bridge Activation (2016-52987) (Box 36, Folder 447)
  - Ohr-O'Keefe Museum of Art - Five New Campus Buildings, Documentary (2010-0195), 2009-2012 (Box 36, Folder 450)
  - One Laptop per Child Association - Laptops for Miami-Dade School System (2011-3082) (Box 36, Folder 451)
  - Opa-Locka Community Development Corporation - Activating Downtown Opa-Locka through THRIVE Campus's Urban Farm, Urban Market, and Innovation Lab (2017-53894) (Box 37, Folder 466)
  - Our City Thoughts - Our City Thoughts (2013-46598), 2013-2014 (Box 38, Folder 483)
  - Partners for Parks, Inc. - Open Streets 704 (2017-54645) (Box 39, Folder 488)
  - Payne-Lake Community Partners - Home Ownership on St. Paul's East Side (2004-0325), 2004-2008 (Box 39, Folder 492)
  - Pennsylvania State University - Pilot: A Census of Connectivity (2016-53201) (Box 40, Folder 498)
  - Pennsylvania Horticultural Society - Library Gardens Initiative Planning (2016-52823) (Box 40, Folder 500)
  - People Acting in Community Together - Bridging the Digital Divide (2013-45519), 2011-2014 (Box 40, Folder 502)
  - People's Emergency Center - Block Party in a Box (2015-50728), 2015-2016 (Box 40, Folder 503)
  - People's Emergency Center - Block Party in a Box (2013-47862), 2013-2014 (Box 40, Folder 505)
  - Performing Arts Center Trust, Inc. - The Masterworks Collection (2010-0268), 2008-2014 (Box 40, Folder 506)
  - Philadelphia Area Cooperative Alliance - 20 Book Clubs, 20 Cooperative Businesses: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52514), 2016-2017 (Box 41, Folder 512)
  - Philadelphia Chinatown Development Corporation - Sidewalk Stories (2017-54045) (Box 41, Folder 513)
  - The Philadelphia Foundation - On the Table, Philadelphia (2017-53758) (Box 41, Folder 517)
  - The Philadelphia Foundation - Supplemental Grant (2009-0270), 2009-2017 (Box 42, Folder 518-519)
  - Philadelphia Industrial Development Corporation - Campaign to Renew Philadelphia, Phase 2 (2016-52033), 2013-2016 (Box 42, Folder 522)
  - Philadelphia Public School Notebook - The Notebook, Knight Community Information Challenge (2012-0158), 2009-2013 (Box 43, Folder 534)
  - Philadelphia Social Innovation Lab - Innovation Lab (2012-3647), 2012-2015 (Box 43, Folder 535)
  - Platform - Pilot (2017-53970) (Box 44, Folder 556)
  - Pop Tech Institute - Pop Tech Impact Fund (2012-0283), 2011-2012 (Box 45, Folder 561)
  - P. L. Dodge Foundation, Inc. - Self-Help Legal Tool (2013-46461), 2011-2014 (Box 45, Folder 562)
  - Portland State University - Electorate Vote Research (2015-51590), 2013-2015 (Box 45, Folder 565)
  - Portland State University - Who Votes for Mayor? Pilot Study (2014-50272), 2013-2015 (Box 45, Folder 566)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - Future of the American City: Miami (2017-54610), 2014-2017 (Box 45, Folder 575)
  - Project TF - Hack2040, Miami (2015-51595) (Box 46, Folder 590)
  - Public Design Studio - Cities Plus: Architecture and Design Talent for Municipalities (2016-52095), 2016-2017 (Box 47, Folder 598)
  - Public Design Studio - Cities Plus: Architecture and Design Talent for Municipalities (2015-51746), 2015-2017 (Box 47, Folder 599)
  - Puerto Rico Community Foundation - Increasing Rural Access to Information: Knight Community Information Challenge (2011-0130), 2010-2013 (Box 48, Folder 608)
  - Queen City Forward - Neighborhood Innovation Strategy (NIS) (2015-50492) (Box 48, Folder 610)
  - Queens University of Charlotte - Increasing Charlotte's Digital Connectivity (2015-50837), 2012-2015 (Box 48, Folder 611)
  - Queens University of Charlotte - Creating a New Knight-Crane Hall (2015-51691) (Box 48, Folder 612)
  - Que Pasa TV - Weekly Television Newscast (2015-51052), 2013-2015 (Box 48, Folder 616)
  - Razoo Foundation - National Day of Giving, Ideas into Action (2014-48692) (Box 48, Folder 620)
  - Reading Terminal Market Corporation - Breaking Bread, Breaking Barriers: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52515), 2015-2016 (Box 48, Folder 622)
  - Refresh Miami, Inc. - Miami Tech and Startup Community Initiatives (2015-51711), 2014-2017 (Box 48, Folder 624)
  - Refresh Miami, Inc. - Monthly Workshops and Hackathons (2013-43012), 2011-2014 (Box 48, Folder 625)
  - Regents of the University of Michigan - Sensors in a Shoebox: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52494) (Box 49, Folder 629)
  - Robins Air Force Base 21st Century Partnership - Communications Initiatives (2013-46271), 2011-2014 (Box 50, Folder 642)
  - St. Paul Chamber of Commerce Foundation Inc. - Central Station Activation (2016-52964) (Box 51, Folder 655)
  - The Saint Paul Foundation - Knight Neighborhood Challenge (2013-47234), 2011-2016 (Box 51, Folder 656)
  - The Saint Paul Foundation - Central Corridor Funders Collaborative (CCFC) (2011-0039), 2009-2013 (Box 51, Folder 657)
  - The Saint Paul Foundation - Supplemental Grant to Donor Advised Fund (2009-0271), 2009-2016 (Box 51, Folder 658)
  - Saint Paul Riverfront Corporation - Downtown Vitality Vision (2017-54689) (Box 51, Folder 659)
  - Saint Paul Riverfront Corporation - Downtown Development Framework (2016-53489) (Box 51, Folder 660)
  - San Antonio Area Foundation - NOWCastSA / Texas Week (2010-0104), 2008-2011 (Box 52, Folder 666)
  - San Francisco Planning and Urban Research Association - Supporting San Jose's Nationally Imported Urban Growth Plan (2014-48597) (Box 52, Folder 668)
  - San Francisco Planning and Urban Research Association - Building A Major New Civic Organization In San Jose (2013-46075), 2011-2013 (Box 52, Folder 669)
  - San Jose Downtown Association - San Pedro Squared, Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50836), 2012-2015 (Box 52, Folder 672)
  - San Jose Downtown Association - Street Life Plan and Public Space Activation Projects (2015-50959), 2012-2017 (Box 52, Folder 673)
  - San Jose Downtown Association - Public Space Activation and Street Life Initiation (2014-48652), 2011-2015 (Box 52, Folder 674)
  - San Jose Public Library Foundation - Early Learning Preschool Program Strategy (2017-54727) (Box 52, Folder 681)
  - San Jose Parks Foundation - Summer in St. James Park (2015-50720) (Box 52, Folder 682)
  - Santa Barbara Foundation - NewSource, Knight Community Information Challenge (2012-0151), 2010-2013 (Box 53, Folder 686)
  - Sant La Haitian Neighborhood Center - Community Support and Counseling, Census Outreach, and Naturalization Outreach (2010-1573), 2009-2010 (Box 53, Folder 687)
  - Sapling Foundation - TED Platform (2012-0346), 2011-2014 (Box 53, Folder 688)
  - School of Arts and Culture at the Mexican Heritage Plaza - The MayFeria: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52516), 2013-2017 (Box 53, Folder 693)
  - Scout - South Philly's Stoop (2015-50671) (Box 54, Folder 699)
  - SFMade, Inc. - Manufacture San Jose (2017-55175) (Box 54, Folder 703)